const questions = [
    {
        question: "In The Sword in the Stone, what does Merlin call The Greatest Force on Earth?",
        answer: "Love",
        choices: ["Love", "Magic", "Arthur", "Water"]
    },
    {
        question: "In Aladdin, what is the name of Jasmine’s pet tiger?",
        answer: "Rajah",
        choices: ["Rajah", "Tigey", "Zara", "Kintaro"]
    },
    {
        question: "How did Walt’s Brother Roy propose to his wife Edna?",
        answer: "By telegram",
        choices: ["By telegram", "By phone", "In person", "By mail"]
    },
    {
        question: "What author wrote the book that the animated feature The Jungle Book is based on?",
        answer: "Rudyard Kipling",
        choices: ["Rudyard Kipling", "L. Frank Baum", "C. S. Lewis", "Roald Dahl"]
    },
    {
        question: "When does Mary Poppins say she will leave the Banks’ house?",
        answer: "When the wind changes",
        choices: ["When the wind changes", "When the story is over", "When the children grow up", "When the money runs out"]
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the farm where the Barnstormer is located?",
        answer: "Goofy’s Wise Acre Farm",
        choices: ["Goofy’s Wise Acre Farm", "Goofy's Plantation", "Goofy Acres", "Goofy's Good Garden"]
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the man that supplied the synthesized voice for the Main Street Electrical Parade from 1979 to 1991?",
        answer: "Jack Wagner",
        choices: ["Jack Wagner", "Paul Frees", "Corey Burton", "Thurl Ravenscroft"]
    },
    {
        question: "What are the names of the 2 trouble makers in Cranium Command in EPCOT?",
        answer: "Tad and Rico",
        choices: ["Tad and Rico", "Chad and Nico", "Rad and Pico", "Fad and Fico"]
    },
    {
        question: "What is the motto for the Rescue Aid Society in The Rescuers?",
        answer: "We never fail to do what is right.",
        choices: ["We never fail to do what is right.", "We always get our man.", "No case is out of reach.", "If you dream it, we can do it."]
    },
    {
        question: "In Dumbo, where is Mrs. Jumbo when the stork delivers her baby?",
        answer: "In the circus train",
        choices: ["In the circus train", "In the circus tent", "In the woods", "In the street"]
    }
]